So in this video, we're going to look at
how we change plans,
how we track changes across them,
how traqplan is really just
amazing at showing the changes
between projects from one
reporting period to the next.
if we expand a simple event plan,
we can see more than
one version in that plan.
Right now, we're gonna
make some changes to it
and watch what happens
as we make those changes.
Here, we will move the venue.
So we shall pull up back
to the left a little bit.
And for some others, we
think that the infrastructure
is going to take a little bit longer.
So let's move that to the right.
And you can see if we
flip between those two [versions] ,
the venue is moving.
And also, the
infrastructure change we've just made
is also really clearly shown.
But there's a better
way to actually show these
without having to flip
between one view and another.
And that is simply to
make the older version
a comparison baseline.
And once we do that, you
can see that what has appeared
is a green line showing
that venue has got better [ie. happening sooner than it was before]
in the most recent
version, and some red lines
showing that the infrastructure project
has slipped a little bit.
That is by far the cleanest
way of showing changes
between one view and another.
And this is really important,
because the first time you show Traqplan
to your bosses,
they're gonna love it.
But the second month you show them,
they're gonna say it still looks great,
but what's changed?
and this works for Microsoft project
imports, it'll soon work for Primavera P6
and any plans you made on
Traqplan natively
and with our free trials
and our free tier there's no excuse for
not leveling up your stakeholder
communications. Join us at traqplan.com